# MD. SOROWAR MAHABUB RABBY

CEO & Founder, চলো programming শিখি TA, Dept. of CSE, IIUC



## **Summary**

I'm a Versatile And Responsible Person With Knowledge And Background In Computer Science And Engineering. I'm A Hard Working, Honest Individual. I'm A Good Timekeeper, Always Willing To Learn New Things And New Skills. I'm Friendly, Helpful And Polite And Have A Good Sense Of Humor. I Have Good Listening And Communication Skills. I Have A Creative Mind And I'm Always Up For New Challenges. My short term goals include earning a job and then get involved in work where i can utilize skill and creatively involve myself with system That effectively contributes to the growth of organization. My long term goal is to become a leading expert in computer related fields by serving in a respectable position.

## **Experience**

#### CEO & Founder || Head Instructor চলো programming শিখি | Feb2021 - present

I have an online Competitive Programming Course under the platform চলো programming শিখি, Completed 3 Batches. Other two Instructor & two TA also work in my Course.

## Teaching Assistant Dept. of CSE IIUC | July 2021 - present

I take lab classes with my Teacher under my dept. in IIUC. I check, grade, supervise the students during lab classes.

#### **Campus Ambassador**

II am working as Campus Ambassador under different learning platform.

## **Awards**

- Awarded Meritorious Reception, Issued by Creative Organization at International Islamic University Chittagong (Sep 2021)
- Awarded any other Scholarships from different Organization in previous educational life.

## **Education**

### Int' Islamic University Chittagong Bachelor of Science | 2020 - present

- Executive Member, 2020/21, Hult Prize at IIUC
- Executive Member, 2022/23, IIUC Data Science Research Group
- Ambassador, ICT Olympiad & Great Learning

### Feni Government College Science Group | 2017 - 2019

- Attended from July, 2017 to June, 2019
- Passed HSC Examination
- Member, 2018/19, FGC Science Club

#### Al-Hera School & College Science Group | 2004 - 2017

## **Skills**

- Teaching/Tutoring
- Communication, Management
- Team Leadership
- Motivational & Public Speaking
- Microsoft Office
- · Problem Solving
- Web Design & Development

## **Contact**

- +8801521 564157, +8801961537181
- in linkedin.com/in/sorowar-cse
- Baroiyerhat, Mirsarai, Chattogram

